{
    "id": "d8bdfa13630947598e8d95b16cf533df",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The principal called …………….. an explanation from the students.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "forth",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "99f1f24295b14b0599bd9d20a492223b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will happily carry ………………. your instructions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "off",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "901a88a68d1249e1a6273320dd12ac8b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The stain wouldn’t come ……………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "in",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "27774122df0844508812b528c8af500f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The actor carried ……………….. his role brilliantly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ab804bf8b8a84ba887f5760b876e2ffb"
        },
        {
            "question": "The manager called me …………….. and demanded an explanation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "df7af46b2f2f4eeaa5a3cd031b9853a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was called ……………….. to make a speech.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "upon"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "495f6d7a92ac4c978a636792ce6a5e99"
        },
        {
            "question": "How did you come ……………….. that necklace?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "by",
                "across"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "56d5afc8c2b84fb6817d52b30968a326"
        },
        {
            "question": "Fear can bring …………….. a heart attack.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9d1df0f8f18142dcb241aa68df145fbc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Somebody had broken ……………. through the back door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "off",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3bd075ad1d38491c8510016d09974c8d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Four prisoners have broken ……………….. of the prison.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "away",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ae026e7230a64c76bddf6882b46504bc"
        }
    ]
}